sapphirefoxx.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | SapphireFoxx.com

### Effective May 30, 2014:

SapphireFoxx.com is an online service that allows paid subscribers to access content and that allows its members to set up personal profiles. SapphireFoxx.com members can view each other’s profiles, upload images, author forums postings, and author comments on the site.

SapphireFoxx.com does not sell personal information about its members to any third party, including but not limited to e-mail addresses and names.  
SapphireFoxx.com will not share any individual personal information with third parties except as required by law.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, SapphireFoxx.com may disclose personal information provided to it by its members or customers to appropriate third parties in order to: (x) comply with any court order or other legal obligation, (y) enforce or apply SapphireFoxx.com’s Terms of Use, or (z) to protect the rights, property, or safety of SapphireFoxx.com, our members, or others. SapphireFoxx.com may disclose and transfer personal information provided to it by its members or customers to a buyer in the event of a sale of all or part of SapphireFoxx.com’s business (whether by asset sale, merger, or otherwise) where customer information is part of the assets being transferred to the buyer. SapphireFoxx.com collects user submitted information such as name and email address to verify users and to provide basic information to other users. Members may provide additional information at their discretion such as location and personal biographies. Additional information is not required for membership to SapphireFoxx.com. Members may remove their information from the system at any time and SapphireFoxx.com will not keep a member’s information for any longer than is necessary to provide its services.

SapphireFoxx.com logs IP addresses of visiting users for statistical purposes and to maintain the integrity of our copyrights and Terms of Service. IP’s are not shared with any third party.

From time to time, SapphireFoxx.com may provide demographic and statistical information to prospective partners for the purposes of securing advertising and/or for general promotion of the website. This disclosure will not share any personal information of individual users but is intended to give a broad overview of SapphireFoxx.com’s membership.

SapphireFoxx.com uses cookies to store login information and to record settings to a user’s local computer. This stored data does not attempt to “mine” any other information from a user’s system or to collect information on sites outside the SapphireFoxx.com family of websites.

SapphireFoxx.com takes great care to protect its users personal information but cannot unconditionally guarantee the security of its database from outside attack or compromise.

SapphireFoxx.com allows members to post URL’s that may take users to other websites. SapphireFoxx.com can make no guarantees as to the Privacy Policies of these sites.

SapphireFoxx.com will update this Privacy Policy from time to time and alert users of the changes via the SapphireFoxx.com online news post or alert system. It is the responsibility of the user to be aware of the current policy.

Questions about SapphireFoxx.com’s privacy should be directed to: TheSapphireFoxx@gmail.com
